

# Thu Hang Le

# Graduate Statistician/ Data Analyst

## My Contact

Marsfield, NSW 2122

Manglth@gmail.com

0481-916-143

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hangIth

waiting for PR granted

## **Education Background**

- Macquarie University Masters of Applied Statistics Completed in Dec 2022 WAM 84.8
- University of Queensland Master of Project Management
- Vietnam National University, Hanoi Bachelor of Science

## **Technical Skills**

- R
- SOL
- Tableau
- Excel Data Analysis
- Python
- Data Visualisation
- · Statistical Modeling
- · Data Analysis

### **Soft Skills**

- · Accomplished at partnership management with stakeholders from both private and government sectors.
- · Well adapted to different working styles of project partners and stakeholders.
- Experienced in working in a team from diverse backgrounds and cultures.
- Data-driven problem solver.

#### **About Me**

A fresh graduate of Applied Statistics with a Distinction average, indepth data manipulation knowledge and skilled in analytics tools such as R, SQL, Tableau, and Excel. I'm seeking an opportunity to apply and further learn data manipulation methods and use the latest computational techniques to analyse and interpret data. I have more than six years of experience managing complete development project life cycles for a UN agency and NGOs, involving data collection and analysis for proposal writing, M&E and decision-

## **Professional Experience**

#### **Avant Mutual | Data Entry Officer**

2022 (casual)

Key responsibilities:

Reviewing, verifying and compiling data in the database system.

#### Oxfam in Viet Nam | Program Officer

2018 - 2019

Key responsibilities:

Design and implementation management of a series of gender and development projects, delivered in partnership with both nongovernment organisations and government agencies.

#### International Labour Organization | Project Coordinator

2015 - 2017

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1.5m portfolio of projects aimed at improving labour practices in private sector enterprises in Viet Nam.

#### Care int. in Viet Nam | Project Manager

2010 - 2014

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1m portfolio of projects aimed at delivering public health interventions for disadvantaged and vulnerable communities.

## **Achievements**

- Successfully managed all projects in charge, including delivering on time, within budget, and to the agreed quality specifications.
- Achieved a full scholarship for the master's program at Queensland University.
- · Attained a scholarship for outstanding students from the Vietnam Ministry of Education and Training for three years.